secsports.com 2008-06-15

# www.secsports.com - SECSports.com Privacy Policy

SECSports.com Privacy Policy

* * *

At SECSports.com, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. SECSports.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Accordingly, children under 13 years old may be restricted from participating in certain activities, contests, and transactions on SECSports.com. 

SECSports.com works with (and may provide links to) third party sites that offer features described on SECSports. Such third parties may permit children under the age of 13 to register on their sites in accordance with their respective privacy policies. However, SECSports.com does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are under 13 years old. 

Please read this Privacy Policy ("Policy") for an explanation of how we will treat your personal information. By using SECSports.com, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our site. If we make any material changes to the Policy, those changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what personal information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information may be disclosed. Since this Policy may change from time to time, you should check back periodically. Your continued use of SECSports.com following the posting of changes to the Policy will signal your acceptance of such changes. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Policy, please contact [paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com](mailto:paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com). 

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

 **1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site;**

 **2\. The organization collecting the information;**

 **3\. How the information is used;**

 **4\. With whom the information may be shared;**

 **5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;**

 **6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control**

**1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site**

As stated above, SECSports.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. SECSports.com does not collect personally identifiable information through the site unless you provide that information during registration for our contests or offers. Information required to participate in our contests or offers may vary but will typically include your first and last name; address including city, state, zip code and country; complete date of birth; and e-mail address; and, in the case of making purchases, a credit card number and expiration date. You may also be requested to provide a username and password for certain features. SECSports.com will maintain all of the personal information submitted by you in secured servers behind corporate firewalls. 

**2\. The organization collecting the information**

SECSports.com is operated by Host Communications. Host Communications is located at 546 East Main Street, Lexington, KY 40508. Please contact [paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com](mailto:paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com) for more information. 

**3\. How the information is used**

SECSports.com may use information provided at registration or information obtained through third parties as your intention to sign up for one of our contests or offers. The use of information provided at registration or obtained through third parties may also be provided to SECSports.com corporate sponsors. 

SECSports.com uses "cookie" technology. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Such technology is an industry standard and is used by most major Web sites. SECSports.com will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. In order to effectively use the site and some of its features, your browser must accept cookies. 

Users should be aware that SECSports.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for SECSports.com. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features available on SECSports.com. 

SECSports.com tracks certain general usage pattern information, including what pages people visit and how long they have been registered users. SECSports.com may log users' IP addresses (the group of four numbers separated by periods, such as 123.45.64.89, that identifies a particular host computer) for the purposes of system administration, site tracking and reporting of aggregate usage information to our marketing and product development teams. 

From time to time, SECSports.com may solicit your opinion to determine your preferences and dislikes in order to provide you with a better product. These surveys are always optional to the user and your decision not to participate in a survey will not affect your status as an SECSports.com user. Should you choose to participate, any information you give us may be used in aggregate form for marketing purposes, and to enhance your overall experience on our site. 

**4\. With whom the information may be shared**

Once again, SECSports.com will not provide any personally identifiable information, other than to its affiliates and corporate sponsors, about you to other third parties without your consent. SECSports.com may, however, provide other third parties with anonymous aggregated information about our users to illustrate trends and patterns. All third parties with whom we share such information will have independent privacy and data collection practices and SECSports.com has no responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

While SECSports.com is careful in choosing its Sponsors and advertisers, we are only responsible for content on our own site. All third parties associated with SECSports.com (including, but not limited to, advertisers, sponsors and other Internet sites) with whom we share information have independent privacy and data collection practices. SECSports.com does not control this collection of information and is neither responsible nor liable for their independent policies or actions. 

**5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information**

You are not required to receive any mailings that you do not wish to receive. During the registration process, you may have the option to sign up to receive newsletters and selected sponsor offers and discounts. You will not receive such information if you do not select such options. If, after you choose to receive such information, you wish to discontinue receiving these items, you may change your subscription preferences by following the instructions provided within the e-mails received. 

**6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control**

SECSports.com has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. The servers for SECSports.com are stored in a physically secure and climate controlled off-site facility. Beyond the physical protection of the servers, we protect against data loss by regularly backing up data, performing consistency checks with independently recorded log files to prevent tampering, and restricting access to information on our servers via several user authentication technologies. Only those employees needed to carry out the business functions will have access to information on individual SECSports.com customers. We train each such employee with respect to the SECSports.com Privacy Policy, and those violating these policies will be subject to disciplinary action. 

It is important to remember that whatever you transmit or disclose online can be collected and used by others or unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In addition, we may disclose information to law enforcement or other government officials if we determine such disclosure to be appropriate, or if we are compelled to disclose it by court order or operation of law. 

LAST UPDATED: September 5, 2002 - SECWEB 090502 Copyright 2002 Host Communications, Inc. All rights reserved. 

**SECSports.com NOTE TO PARENTS**

It is SECSports.com's policy not to solicit any personally identifiable information from children. All SECSports.com online registrants will be required to enter their full name, age, zip code and e-mail address. If SECSports.com determines that a person is under the age of 13, based on the information provided during the registration process, that person will not be permitted to register online for our contests or offers in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Any personally identifiable information that the child may have attempted to enter during the registration process will not be collected or maintained by SECSports.com. Children who indicate that they are under 13 years old will not be able to make credit card purchases or participate in interactive features on SECSports.com that involve the collection and retention of personal information (e.g., entering a contest). 

SECSports.com works with (and may provide links to) third party sites that offer features described on SECSports.com. Such third parties may permit children under the age of 13 to register for these features on their sites in accordance with their respective privacy policies. For more information, please review the privacy policies of each respective third party site. SECSports.com does not knowingly obtain, retain or use information from anyone who indicates that they are under 13 years old. 

If you have any questions or comments, you can contact us at [paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com](mailto:paul.hodges@hostcommunications.com). 

* * *
